# **VLADIMIR DIMITROV**

## **Summary**

Full-stack web developer leveraging a background in marketing to help maximize the user experience for all users on the web. Earned a certificate in full-stack web development from Rutgers, State University of New Jersey Coding Boot camp. Known among staff & classmates for strong attention to detail, creativity, & ready to tackle any project or assignment no matter the complexity.

## Websites, Portfolios, Profiles

- https://dev-vlady.com/
- https://github.com/DevVlady
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/vladimirsdimitrov/

#### **Skills**

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- SASS
- Node.js

- Express.js
- React.js
- MySQL
- MongoDB
- jQuery

- JSON
- Heroku
- Github
- Bootstrap

## **Experience**

01/2019 - 08/2019

Choice Bank Golden Valley, MN

#### **Senior Account Manager**

- Actively developing new business & expanding existing customer relationships through networking, tabling events, & visiting local businesses.
- Review products & services of existing clients to ensure they utilize all their services to help them maximize growth & success to their full potential.

02/2017 - 01/2019

Venture/Choice Bank Golden Valley, MN

#### **Account Manager II**

- Managing new/existing book of business by conducting regular customer reviews to ensure my clients have all the products and services needed to maximize growth.
- Creating brand awareness in the community by attending local network events.

08/2015 - 02/2017

Choice Bank Golden Valley, MN

#### **Account Executive**

- Providing exceptional service by working closely with bank officers to strengthen and expand core
  customer relationships while resolving client issues that arise to improve their business workflow &
  add efficiency.
- Promote deposit products & services to new/existing clients in order to help grow their business & ensure their financial business needs are met.

02/2015 - 08/2015

Venture Bank

**Senior Customer Service Rep** 

Bloomington, MN

- Respond promptly to our client's immediate needs related to transaction processing, online banking access & deposit account functionality & records.
- Use generalist knowledge to interact with and make appropriate referrals to both internal & external customers.

02/2014 - 09/2014

Robert Half Intl Bloomington, MN

### **Staffing Manager**

 Managed full-cycle recruiting, including sourcing, interviewing, offering jobs, and negotiating contracts.

01/2013 - 02/2014

Wells Fargo Eden Prairie, MN

#### **Personal & Small Business Banker**

 Consulted with small business customers to determine needs and means and propose personalized banking solutions.

02/2011 - 01/2013

Wells Fargo Eden Prairie, MN

### **Personal Banker**

 Partnered with loan and mortgage officers and financial advisors to provide clients with optimal financial solutions.

## **Projects**

Budget Tracker | GitHub: https://github.com/DevVlady/Progressive Budget

**Deploy Link:** <a href="https://my-progressive-budget.herokuapp.com/">https://my-progressive-budget.herokuapp.com/</a>

- Budget tracker is an application which allows the user to log their expenses and allow them to keep better track of their expenses.
- HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Express.js, Node.js, PWA, MongoDB & Heroku

Dev Hangout | GitHub: https://github.com/DevVlady/Dev-Hangout

**Deploy Link:** <a href="https://dev-hangout.herokuapp.com/">https://dev-hangout.herokuapp.com/</a>

- An application used to connect developers across the country where they can chat, share project ideas, & provide resources.
- HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Express.js, Node.js, Socket.io, GitHub API, jQuery & MySql

Fitness Tracker | GitHub: https://github.com/DevVlady/Fitness Tracker

**Deploy Link:** <a href="https://fitness-health-tracker.herokuapp.com/">https://fitness-health-tracker.herokuapp.com/</a>

- Fitness tracker is a fitness application which allows athletes to log and review their workouts in order to help them reach their fitness goals.
- HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Express.js, Node.js, MongoDB & Heroku

## **Education and Training**

© 01/2021 **Bootcamp Coding Certificate** in Web Development

Camden, NJ Rutgers, The State University Of New Jersey

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3,

JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handelbars.js & ReactJS.

12/2016 **Bachelor of Science** in Marketing

Saint Paul, MN Metropolitan State University

● 05/2014 General Education

Bloomington, MN Normandale Community College